如果你回答Async Task(异步任务)，那么你是正确的。
If you answered Async Task, then you are correct.
为了理解我们为什么选择Async Task(异步任务)作为答案
To understand why we chose Async Task as the answer,
我们可以看一下开发人员文档。在这个API
we can check the developer documentation. In this API
指南里关于进程和线程中，我们可以滑到
guide on processes and threads, we can scroll to the
Worker threads的部分。那么,如果你需要的话
Worker threads section. Right away, if you want to follow
链接就在下边。说明一下，我在这举个例子,
along, the link is included below. Say, for example, that
如果你想从这个网址上下载一张图片
you want to download an image from the network
并且你想更新这个
at this URL and then you want to update the
用户界面以便显示这个位图。那么，机智的你
UI so that it displays this bitmap. Well, creating
就应该新建一个你自己的线程去下载图片
your own thread to download the image is a
但是还有更重要的事情要做，那就是
valid option, but there's a lot of overhead to
确保你的应用程序真正意义上的线程安全。在
handle in making you app actually thread safe. After
你下载完你的照片后，你并不能马上更新这个
you download your image, you cannot directly update the
后台线程的用户界面。但是，Android里边却有几个
UI from a background thread. However, Android has several
选项在运行代码以此从其他线程中
options to run code that manipulates the UI to
来运行操作用户界面。在这个例子中，
run from other threads. In this example, yet another
另一个可运行状态被建立，就是为了得到主线程传回要求更新图像的位图结果。
runnable is created to get the bitmap result back onto
更新图像的位图结果。这种解决方案
the main thread to update the image view. This solution
是有一点小麻烦因为你不得不管理两个
is a little cumbersome because you have to manage two
可运行的状态。为了简化这个复杂性我们可以用
runnables here. To abstract away this complexity we can use
一个异步任务然后再把她分离。
an async task and then to kick off the async
例如，当有人点击一个按钮时，你
task. For example, when someone clicks a button, then you
只需要初始化这个任务，然后你就可以在这上边调用执行，
just initialize the task, and then you can call execute
然后传输所有必要的参数。
on it, and then pass in any parameters that are needed.
注意！当你在扩展异步类的时候，
Notice that when you're extending the Async class, there's a
有几个需要你指定的泛型。第一个就是
couple of generics that you need to specify. The first is
将要被传递到
the type that will be passed into the do in
后台方法的类型。所以，如果你想在这个图片网站中传递
background method. So, if you want to pass in this image URL
一个指定的字符串作为后台
that is specified string here and then in doing background
你就会得到一个字符串参数。第二个呢就是
you'll get a string parameter. The second one is for the
工程的类型，当你的更新作为一个任务被执行并且有进展的时候你就会需要这个类型
type of object that you'll get when you get progress
你就会需要这个类型。我们在这里就不使用了，
updates as a task gets executed. We're not using that here,
所以把它指定为空的也是可以的。第三种类型就是结果的类型
so it's okay to specify that as void. And the third type is type of results
也就是当我们将要通过onPostExecute方法传送回主线程时需要的类型。
that we'll be sending back to the main thread through the onPostExecute method